<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>

	<VFEI_InsectTerritoryScale>Infested area</VFEI_InsectTerritoryScale>
	<VFEI_Infestation>Infestation</VFEI_Infestation>
	<VFEI_InfestationTooltip>Whether this tile is under the effects of an insectoid infestation.

Areas around insectoid hives are often teeming with insects, with various insect-built structures affecting the environment. Infestations are much more likely to occur, and travelling parties may find roaming insectoids.</VFEI_InfestationTooltip>
	<VFEI_Present>Present</VFEI_Present>
	<VFEI_SettleWarning>This tile is near an insectoid hive, so there will be an ever-present insectoid influence on it. Infestations will happen every {0} days. Large infestations are much more likely to happen, and may occur anywhere, not just in dark areas. Megaspiders, spelopedes and megascarabs are roaming free, and travelling caravans may have to fend off insectoid swarms.</VFEI_SettleWarning>
	
	<VFEI_LarvaeTimeSpawn>{0} before next swarmling spawn.</VFEI_LarvaeTimeSpawn>
	<VFEI_NoMoreSpawningAllowed>Queen is resting.</VFEI_NoMoreSpawningAllowed>
	
	<VFEI2_RoyalInsectJelly>Royal insect jelly fullness:</VFEI2_RoyalInsectJelly>
	<VFEI2_Chemfuel>Chemfuel fullness:</VFEI2_Chemfuel>
	<VFEI2_Chitin>Shedding chitin in:</VFEI2_Chitin>
	<VFEI_CocoonInsectSpawnIn>{0} before insect spawn.</VFEI_CocoonInsectSpawnIn>
	<VFEI_CreatingCocoon>{0} to create cocoon</VFEI_CreatingCocoon>
	<VFEI_CannotPlaceCloseToOtherCreeper>Cannot be placed close to other creeper.</VFEI_CannotPlaceCloseToOtherCreeper>
	<VFEI_Insectoids>Insectoids</VFEI_Insectoids>
	<VFEI_ChooseInsectoidColor>Choose insectoid {0} color</VFEI_ChooseInsectoidColor>
	<VFEI_DefenderDesc>Defender insectoids vigilantly protect their hive by attacking any hostile entities that come within a designated radius.</VFEI_DefenderDesc>
	<VFEI_HunterDesc>Hunter insectoids proactively search for and hunt wildlife near their hive, bringing back and storing kills for communal consumption.</VFEI_HunterDesc>
	<VFEI_WorkerDesc>Worker insectoids are tasked with constructing and maintaining insectoid-specific structures, as well as performing essential hauling and mining duties.</VFEI_WorkerDesc>
	<VFEI_InsectoidWillBeSpawnedIn>{0} will be spawned in: {1}</VFEI_InsectoidWillBeSpawnedIn>
	<VFEI_SpawningStoppedMaxCapacity>Spawning stopped: maximum amount reached.</VFEI_SpawningStoppedMaxCapacity>
	<VFEI_AlreadyActivated>already activated</VFEI_AlreadyActivated>
	<VFEI_OnCooldown>will be available in {0}</VFEI_OnCooldown>
	<VFEI_OtherThumperIsActive>other thumper is active</VFEI_OtherThumperIsActive>
</LanguageData>