<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Vanilla Factions Expanded - Insectoids 2</name>
	<author>Oskar Potocki, xrushha, Taranchuk, Sarg Bjornson</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>OskarPotocki.VFE.Insectoid2</packageId>
	<description>Dive into the "Vanilla Factions Expanded - Insectoids 2" mod and experience a thrilling expansion of the insectoid universe in the game. Here’s what you can look forward to:

Summon and Battle New Bosses: Get ready to face off against new and formidable insectoid bosses. Research and build thumpers to summon these bosses and test your combat skills!

Build and Manage Your Hive: Ever wanted to run your own insectoid hive? Now you can! Harvest resources, breed new types of insectoids, and create a bustling hub of activity.

New Structures and Defenses: From unique walls that only your insectoids can build to defensive structures that protect your colony, this mod introduces a variety of innovative constructions to enhance your gameplay.

Dynamic Combat Challenges: Prepare for unexpected raids and battles. The mod changes how insectoid attacks unfold, making each encounter a unique challenge.

Engaging Quests and World Events: Participate in new quests and world events that revolve around the insectoid infestation. Whether defending against a swarm or initiating one, there's never a dull moment.

Research and Innovation: Unlock new technologies and discover the secrets of the insectoids through dedicated research projects, enhancing your gameplay and giving you the edge in survival.</description>
	<modIconPath IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">UI/VELogo</modIconPath>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>